https://www.hockeyshot.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Hassle Free ReturnsPrice Match GuaranteeWarrantyShippingCustomer SatisfactionPrivacy PolicyTerms of Use
Hassle Free ReturnsPrice Match GuaranteeWarrantyShippingCustomer SatisfactionPrivacy PolicyTerms of Use
Privacy Policy
LAST UPDATED: SEPTEMBER 29, 2020
OUR PLEDGE
HockeyShot Inc. (“HockeyShot”, “we”, “us” or “our”) respects your privacy and pledges to earn and keep your trust. All personal information that we collect from you is maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) and will not be used in ways that are contrary to this Policy. “Personal information” is any information that identifies you, or by which your identity could be deduced. Business contact information is a category of personal information (e.g., an individual’s name, business title, business address or business telephone number), which is defined as any information used for the purpose of communicating or facilitating communication with an individual in relation to their employment, business or profession. Organizations can collect, use and disclose business contact information without consent as long as it is used solely for the purpose of communicating or facilitating communication with someone with respect to his/her job.
This policy is incorporated by reference to our Terms of Use.
YOUR CONSENT
In most cases, we will ask you to provide explicit consent before we collect, use or disclose your personal information. Consent may also be implied in other cases through your conduct with us. For example, by providing your personal information and complete registration to create a user account and become a member, you will have consented to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy.
You may withdraw your consent at any time. However, if you choose to withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide you with the full range of services available through our website.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We collect personal information only by lawful and fair means and not in an intrusive way. In most cases, we collect personal information directly from you, such as through online information forms if you submit an inquiry to us. While we may also use the information that you provided when you signed up as a member, we will only do so in accordance with this Policy.
Like many other websites, we also use passive tracking technologies and third-party analytics tools to collect information from you. These tools may automatically monitor and track information related to activities on our website, including the methods described below.
Cookies
At times we send your computer a "cookie," a small piece of data that is stored in a file on your hard drive. The use of cookies is standard procedure for websites, and those from our website are secure and do not carry viruses. We use cookies to give you better, more personalized service once you've become a member of our website. This information is for internal use only; we don't share it with others. You're always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our website may not work properly for you if you do.
IP Address Tracking
All computers and servers on the Internet use IP addresses to recognize and communicate with each other. Collecting IP addresses allows us to administer and analyze our website and report non-personal information (such as how many visitors we have). When you call up a HockeyShot.com page on your computer, our servers enter the IP address of that computer into a log.
Social Media
We may also collect information if you engage with our website through a third-party social media platform. For example, if you interact with us by using a hashtag on Twitter or Instagram, we and other users of the social media platform may be able to view your profile, depending on your privacy settings on that platform. Your use of third party platforms remains subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies that you have agreed to with such platforms.
HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Personal information collected by us is used internally by our authorized employees for three main purposes: First, we collect personal information to figure out which areas, features, and products are liked the most and found most helpful by our visitors, so we can continue to improve the website. Second, we collect personal information in order to customize the website for our users (for example, it allows us to know if you're a member or not). Finally, we collect personal information to enable our users to participate in sweepstakes, contests, services, and other activities on our website.
Specifically, we collect your personal information as in order to:
Respond to requests and queries you submit to us;
Create and maintain a unique user account for you if you register as a member;
Communicate with you about your account and updates to our website, products and services;
Allow you to submit orders for our products and services through our website;
Process payment transactions and send you the products that you purchase through our online store;
Communicate with you about your purchase orders, or communicate our email newsletter to you, if you make a purchase on our online store or opt-in to receive these communications;
Understand your preferences and tailor offers and services to you based on these preferences; and
Conduct analyses and evaluations to understand consumer trends and usage related to our products in order to improve our websites, services and marketing communications
SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We will never sell or rent your information to third parties. However, we may share your information with other parties in certain situations, such as service providers acting on our behalf to provide services to you.
Your personal information will only be disclosed to third parties in the following circumstances:
when we are required or authorized by law to do so, such as if a court issues a subpoena;
when you have consented to the disclosure;
when the services we are providing to you require us to give your personal information to a third party your consent will be implied, unless you tell us otherwise;
where it is necessary to establish or collect amounts owed to us;
if we engage a third party to provide administrative services to us (such as computer back-up services or archival file storage) and the third party is bound by this Policy;
if the personal information is already publicly known.
Our Partners
We may share your personal information with our business partners when you grant us permission to share the personal data, e.g. by opting-in to email communications from a business partner on the HockeyShot website. Please be aware that these partners are governed by separate privacy policies.
Service Providers
We may share your personal information with our business partners and certain service providers in order to provide services to you, to verify and validate information, and to address customer service matters. Examples of service providers include our payment processor, Shopify Payments. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. If you do not wish for us to provide your personal information to those service providers, we may be unable to provide you with the full range of services available through our website.
Occasionally, we may use service providers outside of Canada to process and/or store personal information for us. Please note that personal information in the custody of these service providers may be subject to access by the law enforcement authorities of those jurisdictions in which the service providers are located. Our Privacy Department, whose contact information is provided below, can provide further information about our policies and practices regarding service providers located outside of Canada and further information about how these service providers, collect, use, disclose or store personal information on our behalf.
Business Change
In the event that our business undergoes a fundamental change, such as a sale or financing, merger, transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets (“Business Change”), we may disclose your personal information to the counterparties to the transaction and their professional advisors as necessary for them to conduct due diligence and to complete the transaction. However, this information would only be disclosed with the requirements that the counterparties and their professional advisors maintain your information as confidential and that any successor to our business only use and disclose your information for those purposes for which you have provided consent to us. Following such Business Change, you may contact the entity to which we disclosed your information with an inquiry concerning the processing of that information.
CONTESTS
From time to time, we offer promotional contests. If you choose to participate in one of our contests, we may collect personal information in order to allow you to participate in that contest. The personal information we collect from the contest may be used in a specific way in relation to that contest. All contest details, including official rules, are posted during the contest period and will disclose how your personal information will be used. Those disclosures shall override anything to the contrary in this Policy with respect to the personal information collected, used and disclosed in connection with that contest. Certain contests conducted on third party social media platforms, such as Facebook, may also be subject to the specific terms and policies of that platform.
EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS
If you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your personal information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. However, aside from our reply to such an email, it is not our standard practice to email you directly unless you request a particular service that involves email communications. You may also have the opportunity to subscribe to an email list or electronic newsletter that will send information about our websites or our advertisers to your email address. We will provide you with the option to change your preferences and opt-out of receiving those communications. You may request at any time that we not email you in the future by clicking the "unsubscribe" link, which will be included at the bottom of any email that you receive from us. If you unsubscribe, we will make reasonable efforts to discontinue these email communications as soon as practicable.
ONLINE BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING
Like many other companies, we engage in online behavioural advertising or interest-based advertising. "Online behavioral advertising” or “interest-based advertising” includes advertisements served to you after you leave our website, encouraging you to return. They also include advertisements that we think are relevant based on your shopping habits or online activities. These advertisements might be served on websites or on apps. They might also be served in emails. These advertisements maybe served by us or other third parties. They might be about our products or other companies' products.
You have some choices when it comes to online behavioural advertising: We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising and the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s Canadian Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising. DAA’s principles are available: https://youradchoices.com/principles and DAA Canada’s principles available: https://assets.youradchoices.ca/pdf/DAAC-ThePrinciples.pdf.
the Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising program provides consumers with the ability to opt-out of having their online behavior recorded and used for advertising purposes.
The Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) also offers a tool for opting-out of the collection of cross-app data on a mobile device for interest-based advertising.
For more information, including how to opt out of having your online behavior collected for advertising purposes or to exercise choice for companies participating in the DAA tool, please see https://youradchoices.com/. Choices you make are both browser and device-specific.
DO NOT TRACK
Our website currently does not respond to Do Not Track signals in browsers. While we collect personal information from you as described in this Policy, we do not collect personal information from you to monitor your online activities across third party websites or online services (also known as behavioral advertising).
Third parties that have content embedded on our website (such as buttons, widgets, and other embedded features or content) may set Cookies on a user’s browser or obtain information about the fact that you visited our website from a certain IP address. Our service providers may also collect personal information as described in the section above through the use of an embedded button or similar technology. We do not authorize third parties to collect any other personal information from our website unless you provide it to them directly.
GENERAL SECURITY & RETENTION
We protect your personal information using commercially reasonable physical, organizational and technical measures. To guard against unauthorized access to your data, we use the latest encryption technologies, implement rigorous password protections, secure our premises and place limits on the number of people who have access to your information.
Your User Account & Password
If you have registered as a member, you are responsible for the security of your password used to login to your user account. Please notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your user account or any other breach of security relating to your account. HockeyShot will not be liable for any loss or damage arising out of your failure to comply with this section. You may be issued a new password or occasionally be required to change your password. We encourage you to create a secure password. The Sign Out link is always available on the top right side of your screen,in the Account dropdown. If you are using a public computer we recommend you sign out after you are done visiting the HockeyShot website.
Retention of Information
We only retain your personal information as long as reasonably necessary for us to complete our dealings with you, or as may be required by law, whichever is longer. If you want to delete your account entirely, please see the section above or contact us at the details below.
REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You have a right to review any of the information that we hold about you and to contact us in order to learn about how we have used it or to whom we have disclosed it. Subject to any exceptions prescribed by law, you can access and correct your personal information and challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information we have about you. We may deny access when required or authorized by law. For example, we may deny access when granting access would have an unreasonable impact on other people’s privacy or when necessary to protect our confidential commercial information and the requested information cannot be severed from the balance of the record in which it is contained. If we deny your request for access to, or refuse a request to correct information, we shall explain why.
If you have a user account, you can review and change the personal information in your member profile at any time. To do that, click the account link at the top of any page.
WE DON’T COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM MINORS
It is our policy not to knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If you are a parent or guardian and you suspect that your child may have submitted personal information to us, please contact us at customersupport@hockeyshot.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will strive to delete such information from our servers as soon as possible.
In general, we collect the same information from children that we collect from other users of our websites, and we use and share such information for the same purposes. We will not knowingly require a child to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity. If at any time a parent or guardian wishes to access, correct, delete, or control the disclosure of personal information provided by his or her child, he or she should contact us at customersupport@hockeyshot.com.
HOW TO PROVIDE A CALIFORNIA MINOR REMOVAL REQUEST
If you are a user under the age of 18 and reside in California, and you wish for your published content to be removed from our website, please provide HockeyShot’s Agent listed below with the following information in a written notice:
Confirmation that you are currently a legal resident of the state of California;
Confirmation that you are under the age of 18 by providing your date of birth;
A description of the exact content that you are seeking to have removed (please provide a URL if possible);
Your full name; and
Your email address.
HockeyShot’s designated Agent for California Minor Removal Requests can be reached as follows:
Service Provider: HockeyShot Inc. Name of Agent for Notice: Copyright Agent By mail: 7025 Langer Drive, Suite 115, Mississauga, ON L5N 0E8 By phone: +1 (888) 417-7468 Email: customersupport@hockeyshot.com (please add “California Minor Removal Request” to the subject line)
CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
Residents of the State of California have the right to request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed certain information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. However, it is our policy to neither disclose personal information, nor to sell such information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without your consent. Read Our CCPA Privacy Notice.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Like many other websites, our website contains links to other third party websites which are not governed by the terms of this Policy (“Linked Sites”). These links are provided for your convenience only and not imply endorsement by us of the Linked Site or any association with its operators. Please be aware that these Linked Sites are governed by separate privacy policies. We encourage you to be aware when you click these links and leave our site. Your use of these Linked Sites is at your own risk.
CHANGES
We may modify this Policy at any time, and such modifications shall be effective as soon as the modified Policy is posted. Accordingly, you agree to review the Policy periodically, and your continued access or use of this website shall be deemed your acceptance of the modified Policy. If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Department at customersupport@hockeyshot.com or by submitting an inquiry on our Contact Us page of this website.
Safe & Secure
Fast Shipping
Train Like The Pros
100% Satisfaction Guaranteed
Hassle Free Returns
Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
